{"title": "Harry Potter!", "listOfQuestions": [{"question": "What is the name of the first book in the Harry Potter series?", "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter and the Sorcerer's Stone", "wrongAnswers": ["Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets", "Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban", "Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "Who is Harry Potter's best friend?", "correctAnswer": "Ron Weasley", "wrongAnswers": ["Hermione Granger", "Neville Longbottom", "Draco Malfoy"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What is the name of the magical sport played on broomsticks in the Harry Potter series?", "correctAnswer": "Quidditch", "wrongAnswers": ["Infernal Quidditch", "Quizzle", "Broomstruck"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What house is known for its bravery and courage at Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry?", "correctAnswer": "Gryffindor", "wrongAnswers": ["Ravenclaw", "Hufflepuff", "Slytherin"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "Who is the headmaster of Hogwarts throughout most of the series?", "correctAnswer": "Albus Dumbledore", "wrongAnswers": ["Severus Snape", "Gilderoy Lockhart", "Remus Lupin"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What magical object allows Harry to see into the memories of others?", "correctAnswer": "Pensieve", "wrongAnswers": ["Time-Turner", "Sneakoscope", "Remembrall"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What type of creature is Dobby?", "correctAnswer": "House-elf", "wrongAnswers": ["Goblin", "Werewolf", "Basilisk"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What is the name of the prison guarded by Dementors in the wizarding world?", "correctAnswer": "Azkaban", "wrongAnswers": ["Nurmengard", "Alcatraz", "Arkham Asylum"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What is Harry's Patronus charm in the shape of?", "correctAnswer": "Stag", "wrongAnswers": ["Otter", "Phoenix", "Werewolf"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "Who is the half-giant teacher of Care of Magical Creatures?", "correctAnswer": "Rubeus Hagrid", "wrongAnswers": ["Gilderoy Lockhart", "Argus Filch", "Sybill Trelawney"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What is the name of the three-headed dog guarding the Philosopher's Stone?", "correctAnswer": "Fluffy", "wrongAnswers": ["Fang", "Norbert", "Aragog"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What type of dragon does Harry face in the Triwizard Tournament?", "correctAnswer": "Hungarian Horntail", "wrongAnswers": ["Chinese Fireball", "Swedish Short-Snout", "Peruvian Vipertooth"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What is the name of the dark wizard who killed Harry's parents?", "correctAnswer": "Lord Voldemort", "wrongAnswers": ["Bellatrix Lestrange", "Gellert Grindelwald", "Salazar Slytherin"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What is the name of the elf who served the Malfoy family?", "correctAnswer": "Dobby", "wrongAnswers": ["Kreacher", "Winky", "Hokey"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What is the name of Hermione's cat?", "correctAnswer": "Crookshanks", "wrongAnswers": ["Mrs. Norris", "Pigwidgeon", "Firenze"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What is the name of the Weasley's magical flying car?", "correctAnswer": "Ford Anglia", "wrongAnswers": ["Knight Bus", "Hogwarts Express", "Thestral Cart"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What is the name of the wizarding village near Hogwarts School?", "correctAnswer": "Hogsmeade", "wrongAnswers": ["Diagon Alley", "Godric's Hollow", "Little Whinging"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "Who is Harry's godfather?", "correctAnswer": "Sirius Black", "wrongAnswers": ["Remus Lupin", "James Potter", "Peter Pettigrew"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What type of spell can repel a Dementor?", "correctAnswer": "Expecto Patronum", "wrongAnswers": ["Stupefy", "Expelliarmus", "Alohomora"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What is the name of the potion that allows the drinker to transform into someone else?", "correctAnswer": "Polyjuice Potion", "wrongAnswers": ["Felix Felicis", "Veritaserum", "Amortentia"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What is the core of Harry's wand made of?", "correctAnswer": "Phoenix feather", "wrongAnswers": ["Dragon heartstring", "Unicorn hair", "Thestral tail hair"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What is the name of Gilderoy Lockhart's tragic autobiography?", "correctAnswer": "Magical Me", "wrongAnswers": ["One Flew Over the Hippogriff's Nest", "Charmingly Conceited", "Fantastic Beasts and How to Avoid Them"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What is the name of the gamekeeper and Care of Magical Creatures professor at Hogwarts?", "correctAnswer": "Rubeus Hagrid", "wrongAnswers": ["Remus Lupin", "Alastor Moody", "Sybill Trelawney"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What is the name of the house elf who serves the Black family?", "correctAnswer": "Kreacher", "wrongAnswers": ["Dobby", "Winky", "Hokey"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What is the name of Harry Potter\u2019s group of loyal friends who help him challenge Lord Voldemort and fight the Death Eaters?", "correctAnswer": "Dumbledore's Army", "wrongAnswers": ["Gryffindor's Pride", "The Order of the Phoenix", "The Marauders"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What is Hermione's Patronus charm in the shape of?", "correctAnswer": "Otter", "wrongAnswers": ["Stag", "Phoenix", "Werewolf"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What are wands made of?", "correctAnswer": "Wood and core materials", "wrongAnswers": ["Wood and vines", "Metal and core materials", "Plastic and core materials"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "The Deluminator is a device in the Harry Potter series that has multiple functions.What does it do?", "correctAnswer": "It captures and releases light.", "wrongAnswers": ["It removes the memory from one person's brain", "It makes things levitate", "It opens doors"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "Peter Pettigrew has nickname Wormtail. Name two other nicknames from the Marauder's Map.", "correctAnswer": "Prongs and Moony", "wrongAnswers": ["Mad-Eye and Tonks", "Snape and Draco", "Moonlight and Twinsoul"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "Who possesses the power of invisibility cloak in Harry Potter series?", "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter", "wrongAnswers": ["Ron Weasley", "Hermione Granger", "Dobby"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What is the Forbidden Forest?", "correctAnswer": "A forest within the grounds of Hogwarts School that has a bad reputation. Many dangerous creatures live or lurk there, and many challenges are set for students, such as detention or Care of Magical Creatures lessons.", "wrongAnswers": ["It's a forest where people can picnic", "A magical party forest", "For students of forbidden ages"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "With which house does Draco Malfoy share a dormitory?", "correctAnswer": "Slytherin", "wrongAnswers": ["Gryffindor", "Hufflepuff", "Ravenclaw"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "Who is the Divination professor at Hogwarts?", "correctAnswer": "Sybill Trelawney", "wrongAnswers": ["Severus Snape", "Pomona Sprout", "Cuthbert Binns"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What is the name of the house elf who dies at the hand of Bellatrix Lestrange?", "correctAnswer": "Dobby", "wrongAnswers": ["Kreacher", "Winky", "Hokey"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What drink can help a person recover from consuming poison?", "correctAnswer": "Bezoar", "wrongAnswers": ["Veritaserum", "Polyjuice Potion", "Felix Felicis"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "Name the Weasley twins.", "correctAnswer": "Fred and George", "wrongAnswers": ["Bill and Charlie", "Percy and Ron", "Ginny and Hermione"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What is the name of the magical map that shows the location and movements of individuals within Hogwarts?", "correctAnswer": "The Marauder's Map", "wrongAnswers": ["The Quidditch Pitch Map", "The Hogwarts Guide", "The Defense Against the Dark Arts Map"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "Who teaches Defense Against the Dark Arts in Harry's sixth year at Hogwarts?", "correctAnswer": "Severus Snape", "wrongAnswers": ["Dolores Umbridge", "Gilderoy Lockhart", "Remus Lupin"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "Who kills Albus Dumbledore in the Harry Potter series?", "correctAnswer": "Severus Snape", "wrongAnswers": ["Bellatrix Lestrange", "Draco Malfoy", "Voldemort"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "Which Horcrux was destroyed last?", "correctAnswer": "Nagini", "wrongAnswers": ["Helga Hufflepuff's Cup", "Tom Riddle's Diary", "Rowena Ravenclaw's Diadem"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What is the name of the wizard who created the Sorcerer's Stone?", "correctAnswer": "Nicholas Flamel", "wrongAnswers": ["Gellert Grindelwald", "Albus Dumbledore", "Sven Sixkiller"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What is Mad-Eye Moody's real name?", "correctAnswer": "Alastor Moody", "wrongAnswers": ["Barty Crouch Jr.", "Kingsley Shacklebolt", "Ernie Macmillan"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "Who is the head of the Department of Magical Law Enforcement in the Ministry of Magic?", "correctAnswer": "Amelia Bones", "wrongAnswers": ["Cornelius Fudge", "Pius Thicknesse", "Rufus Scrimgeour"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What is the name of the spell used to disarm an opponent?", "correctAnswer": "Expelliarmus", "wrongAnswers": ["Stupefy", "Avada Kedavra", "Alohomora"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What is the name of the wizard who takes over as Defense Against the Dark Arts professor at Hogwarts after Gilderoy Lockhart?", "correctAnswer": "Remus Lupin", "wrongAnswers": ["Dolores Umbridge", "Severus Snape", "Barty Crouch Jr."], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What does Harry see in the Mirror of Erised?", "correctAnswer": "His parents", "wrongAnswers": ["Himself as a famous Quidditch player", "A future version of himself", "He doesn't see anyone"], "timeout": 15}, {"question": "What is the name of the ghost who haunts the girls' bathrooms at Hogwarts?", "correctAnswer": "Moaning Myrtle", "wrongAnswers": ["Nearly Headless Nick", "The Bloody Baron", "The Fat Friar"], "timeout": 15}]}